This program is a program that
challenges various things with the
members of the student council to raise
the excitement of the world!
OTTAKU GO back tolasse Place
The day before Halloween
We played critter.
be changed by a special guest
What is this Indian dance that Kaguya
cracks up on watching?
You lad!
HALOWEEEN
Jiggana
hattee one
I'm going to meet a lot of cute girls
on Halloween.
I've done a rehearsal, but I'm so happy
to meet a lot of girls.
I'm going to meet a lot of cute girls
on Halloween.
What a wonderful event!
I'm going to meet a lot of cute girls
on Halloween.
Today's Juri's fortune.
Fortune?
I'm not sure.
I think you're in a good mood today.
So, I'll hit you.
I see.
It's famous to hit.
Can I do it?
Left hand?
Both are fine.
I like left hand.
I can see a smooth line.
I'm afraid I'll be careful.
So, I'll be careful and open my hand.
I'll be in a good mood if I do it.
Thank you.
I'll be careful.
You look serious.
I'm serious.
I think I'll hit you.
But, there are differences between left
and right, so I'll show you various
things.
I'll show you various things.
Let's go.
The first one is Ayu.
She's a very good player.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to our channel.
Y ya so pretty
Kawaii
Love you
Sengine
Give me love
I'm more excited than nervous.
We are MI.
GO.
ROCK ON.
We are Super-Sexy-Sexy-Dream.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you for watching!
It's all because of you
I was born to be a princess
I want you to forget about me
And
Thank you very much
Thank you
Is everyone okay?
Yes
Thank you
I'm going to the concert
Thank you for watching
They are ready to go on.
How's that?
It makes me nervous...
even after I release the hanger.
I'll do my best.
Please subscribe to our channel!
I was walking with you, and I was
expecting a new development
You said we should go to the festival
right after we turned the corner
You said you were much prettier than
the Soviet Union that bloomed in a
rainbow
You said something so smelly
I'm sure you'll disappear into the
crowd
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'll do my best.
I'm sweating.
Wow, I did it!
Tokisen's YouTube.
Oh, my mom.
Oh, yeah. Your mom.
You like Tokisen.
I'm Shinji.
Mom.
I'm Shinji's mom.
Yay, mom!
Thank you for watching.
I really love Becky
It's COOL!
I like it
Crunchy crunchy
Can you hear me?
I can hear you.
Listener.
This is a listener.
I can hear you.
I went to pick up Akita.
I was with Rikinai.
Cut.
No, not yet.
Oh.
We're without an audience.
That's so pretty.
They're like, your costume's pretty.
Risky danger
if you learn even one
correct!
Give me your long eyes
There's no failure
How much is it laughed about?
Just right
For Empire
Yuqing
Event
Cloud suddenly turns to the back!
It's a camera!
The ringing thing after
the cloak is important and
makes us look good in front of the
camera!
We'll call this feeling Antipatic-F
somehow
Skinny Skinny Skinsky Skinsky Skinny
Skinsky
The existence of you is now
I'll go all the way.
The members of Baby-tune said they want
to end Hiori with the best.
It's definitely going to be fun.
I saw the story of Baby-tune's HitoPia
at the rehearsal yesterday.
What's that story?
Hiori's story is always weird.
It was different from what I imagined.
It's a compliment.
Mayama-san told me that I was different
from my image.
She's watching my story.
We're going to do the rehearsal of
Sadonetsu together.
Miu-chan and Miu-chan of Bashon.
We're going to do the rehearsal of
Sadonetsu together.
Everyone is laughing.
I talked a lot with Rima-san and
Abakura-san.
I watched Sanrio's live video a lot.
And yesterday's lesson was a long
panties.
At first, Beni-chan and Arin said,
Hito-chan, you're the same size as
everyone else.
You're not tall, you're like a student
in the growth period.
After that, after a while, I asked
Shiorin,
Are you the same size as everyone else?
I asked her to buy it.
I saw Beni-chan say that.
I thought I was told by Beni-chan and
Arin.
I was embarrassed.
I'm going to be a big girl.
I want to be a big girl.
Hey, letting me kiss your lips
Please come again!
meal,
I'm sure you know what love is.
I'm sure I love you more than anyone
else
Do you know it?
I'm going to finish my makeup now.
Bye bye!
I'm happy every day
It's really good!
It's written here too
It looks like a fan of Kaya.
It's cute!
Look at the back.
This is how we become Toku-san.
Let's go! Hikikari Toku-san!
I'm going to do it from today.
This is the first time to be on the
stage.
Let's go to see the party.
I'll treat you.
No.
Cute.
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to my channel!
I'm going to eat a sandwich.
Which one do you eat? A or Iyaya?
Well...
I don't like Iyaya.
I like it the best.
Let's go to eat tapioca.
I...
Iyaya!
I'm not going to do that.
I'm going to dance.
No.
I like spring.
I really like spring.
Thank you. I like spring, too.
Thank you.
It's like a strawberry confectionery.
Yes.
My birthday is January 5th.
January 5th.
We have the same birthday party.
Yes.
Strawberry confectionery.
And we are the same age.
Yes, we are.
We say happy birthday to each other
every year.
We do.
Yes, we do.
Happy birthday! Thank you! Thank you!
We say that.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's really fun.
I'm excited.
Kiyoi, the genius of the candy.
The genius of the candy.
Kiyoi!
Kiyoi, the genius of the candy.
The genius of the candy.
I don't want to.
I see.
I don't like this.
I don't think I can do this.
You can do it.
Take it away.
I don't want to.
You're a good girl.
I'm a good teacher.
You're good.
I'm going to be scolded.
It's okay.
X Girl Presents
Yellow...
Next is black Tommy-chan
Thank you.
Did you see how I made it?
On the stage, Ce spilled milk.
Haha
Here starts their debut sole는
Hi
Good morning
I'm so scared.
I'm scared.
Ready, go!
Go!
The color of the snow is falling
The spring that is too blue that won't
come true
When your voice mixes with mine
It feels like a dream
Forever and ever
I think I can be by your side
Thanks for watching!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
So I admire you. I stick the Red Gamer
m проводу и ѿерчу обратно.
Later I'll call your footsteps and
count them up.
Because of you I've been smiling many
times already.
Thank you very much.
Kiss me, kiss me, kiss me.
For only the moment I touch you,
modo no koto wo shiretta zubi desu
We are NiziU.
Thank you very much.
We will be back soon.
Thank you.
We will play the medley.
We will start the medley.
Thank you.
I met V-san in the line.
I'm Rittan.
I'm Rittan in the line.
I'm Riko Nakayama.
I'm Riko.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for coming.
I want to wear your costume.
I love this kind of costume.
Please subscribe to this channel.
oh my gosh!!!
To my daisy-colored, enticing woman
I can't stop
We memes just moving language.
We'll be back!
What's your order?
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
We're the Gatten Girls!
Today's a bright and cheerful day
We're spending our time and effort to
make it a good day
Sparkling dreams and bingsu
Our shining eyes are all glowing
It was fun!
How was it, Hitoka-chan?
It was really fun, and I thought the
way everyone was outing was really cute.
I was really happy to talk with
Ebitune-san at rehearsals.
Yeah, we were talking for a long time.
I'm working with Oharu and Julia right
now,
but talking with everyone was really...
I want to remember that I really like
this feeling.
I want to remember.
I love you.
Please remember.
I want to remember.
I'm not sure.
What was it?
I don't know.
The one with the bear.
This one and this one.
It's the bear.
Ah!
It's a bit hard.
It's loose.
Let's do our best.
I think we can talk to 30 people today.
We might be able to see it tomorrow.
Yeah.
I think we can talk to 30 people today.
Yeah, let's focus on this one.
Let's do our best.
We'll do our best.
Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter!
I was singing in a low voice
But I met you
subs by maro!
Thank you very much!
I hope we can sing together.
I hope so.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
Thank you for watching.
I can't get the tipping.
I have to take off my mask.
Thank you for watching!
We've finished the StarPLA festival!
It was really fun to be able to
collaborate with so many StarPLA idols.
We were able to talk to so many
different groups.
We were able to talk more and more.
It was really fun from the rehearsal.
There were so many groups who danced to
our songs.
I was really happy.
I was really happy to see so many
groups who were interested in us.
We performed outside of Japan this
time.
I'm really happy that so many people
liked our live performance.
I feel like we were able to record it.
We were able to meet so many people.
We were able to find so many StarPLA
fans.
We were able to meet so many people.
I'm relieved.
Thank you.
We were able to meet Karen.
We are so tired.
We will be a big group that can do one-
man show in Yokohama someday.
We will do our best.
Thank you.
A scenery you don't know
Come on, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is so beautiful
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I'll draw a fragment of the future
It guides me
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
But when you're lost, remember
Even if it rains, so you can smile
Come on, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day
I play the sound of rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye
Goodbye to me from yesterday
The city lights after the rain sparkle
My heart is like a flower
I'll dry my tears
And wear a rainbow dress